<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anjila Tripathi</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Anjila Tripathi</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 18:07:16 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Event App QA Testing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/event-app-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 18:07:16 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/event-app-case-study/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A comprehensive QA evaluation of an event management app focused on delivering a flawless user experience. Key aspects of the testing process included:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manual Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Conducted thorough testing of user interfaces and features to identify and report bugs and inconsistencies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automated Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Developed and executed automated test scripts using Selenium to streamline testing and enhance coverage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Utilized LoadRunner to simulate peak usage scenarios, optimizing the app’s performance under high traffic conditions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Performed security assessments to identify and address potential vulnerabilities, ensuring the app&amp;rsquo;s security and reliability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The project resulted in a high-quality event management app with improved functionality, performance, and security, providing users with a seamless experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case Study Mobile Application QA Testing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/case-study-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/case-study-one/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A comprehensive QA assessment of a web application aimed at ensuring high performance, reliability, and user satisfaction. The project involved meticulous testing processes, including:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manual Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Thoroughly tested user interfaces and functionality to identify and report bugs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automated Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Developed and executed automated test scripts using Selenium to streamline repetitive testing tasks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Utilized LoadRunner to assess the application&amp;rsquo;s performance under various load conditions, optimizing for better response times and reliability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cross-Browser Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Ensured compatibility across multiple browsers and devices to provide a consistent user experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The project resulted in a robust, high-quality web application with enhanced performance and user satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recipe App QA Testing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/recipe-app-ux-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 18:19:35 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/recipe-app-ux-study/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A thorough QA assessment of a recipe app designed to ensure optimal user experience. The testing process involved:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manual Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Performed detailed testing of app features and functionality to identify and address bugs and inconsistencies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automated Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Created and ran automated test scripts using tools like Selenium to streamline testing and enhance coverage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Usability Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Evaluated the app&amp;rsquo;s user interface and experience to identify areas for improvement and ensure intuitive navigation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Assessed the app&amp;rsquo;s responsiveness and stability under various conditions to optimize performance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Conducted security assessments to safeguard user data and ensure the app&amp;rsquo;s security.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The project resulted in a refined recipe app with enhanced functionality, performance, and user satisfaction, providing a seamless and enjoyable cooking experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QA Testing for Agriculture App</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/ux-case-study-for-agriculture-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 12:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/ux-case-study-for-agriculture-app/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A comprehensive QA evaluation of an agriculture app designed to ensure it effectively serves its target users. The testing process included:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manual Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Thoroughly tested the app’s functionality and user interface to identify and address bugs and inconsistencies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automated Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Developed and executed automated test scripts to cover repetitive testing scenarios and improve efficiency.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Usability Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Assessed the app’s user experience to ensure it was intuitive and met the needs of farmers and agricultural professionals.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Tested the app’s performance under various load conditions to ensure it could handle high traffic periods effectively.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Performed security assessments to protect user data and ensure the app’s integrity.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The project resulted in a high-quality agriculture app with enhanced functionality, usability, and performance, providing users with a reliable and efficient tool for their agricultural needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decrypting Hackathons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/hackathon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-actually-is-this-hackathon-thing&#34;&gt;What actually is this HACKATHON thing?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hackathons, also known as &amp;lsquo;Codefests,&amp;rsquo; are becoming increasingly popular worldwide, but in Nepal, they&amp;rsquo;re a relatively new concept. Contrary to the misconception that hackathons involve hacking into software or security systems, they&amp;rsquo;re creative events where programmers, developers, and innovative minds collaborate to solve specific problems within a set timeframe.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hackathons, derived from &amp;lsquo;hacker&amp;rsquo; (clever programmer) and &amp;lsquo;marathon&amp;rsquo; (endurance), were introduced by the open-source community. These events challenge participants to work continuously on a single project for either 24 or 48 hours, aiming to develop a software prototype that addresses a predefined issue.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFC Codefest 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/cfccodefest2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/cfccodefest2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Codefest 2022, organized by Code for Change, is the first and the biggest&#xA;Hackathon in Nepal, which intends to build a technological solution for any of the&#xA;selected 7 SDGs viz. SDG 3,4,5,9,11,13, and 16, by the students pursuing&#xA;bachelors in technology in Nepal.&#xA;It is a dynamic event in which students who are highly interested in IT can learn&#xA;new concepts, discover new ideas, and garner knowledge in the domain of&#xA;technology which will help them boost their interest and confidence in&#xA;technology and help them shape their future in this exciting field.&#xA;The event reached the students of all 7 provinces and provided them with an&#xA;opportunity and platform to pitch their idea in relation to solving any of the&#xA;proposed SDGs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
